Download subtitles or load it directly from url loadsubs.net
This movie is an adaptation of a novel
about an actual case that happened
Today's weather is cloudy to overcast.
There will be rainfall and snow in
the central areas.
In the early morning, there will be thick
fog in areas near the mountains.
Thick fog will also be seen on west
coast and the mountainous region.
Today's temperature will be similar
to yesterday's.
Seoul is at -2 degrees Celsius.
Dae Jeon is at -2 degrees Celsius.
Gwang Ju is at -1 degree  Celsius.
Mu Jin is at -1 degree Celsius.
You haven't arrived yet?
The fog is too heavy and I don't
even know where I am right now.
You will be reaching soon.
Mu Jin is naturally a place with
thick fog.
What's Song In doing now?
- She is sleeping.
She has been crying aloud for you
and only fell asleep a while ago.
Did she cry a lot?
It happens to all kids who are
separated from their parents.
Don't worry too much.
Just focus on your job.
It wasn't easy to get this job, so make
sure you hold on to it.  Understand?
~=CruCible / SiLenced=~
How long will I need to wait?
Because of thick fog
in the early morning,
you still have to wait a while more.
Excuse me. May I know if there are any
public buses to Ja Ae School from here?
Ja Ae School?
Are you referring to
that School for the Deaf?
That place is a bit remote,
so there is no direct public bus.
A taxi will cost you
at least 50 000 Won.
You are leaving just like this?
I'm running against time now.
Let's talk tomorrow.
If you can,
leave your car here for repair.
Ajussi, what's the matter with you?
(Ajussi - older man, uncle)
How could you just suddenly reverse
without checking your mirrors?
What are you talking about?
I did not even move my car.
Ajussi, are you bullying me
because I'm a woman?
You have picked the wrong person
this time.
Boss, may I borrow your spray?
I'm speechless.
Exactly which car get bumped into?
Miss, I haven't even started my car.
Hey you this person, I predict, you
will get into trouble one of these days.
Boss, come and take a look.
This person is pretty drunk.
What should I do?
Why?
Are you having a drink too many
again last night?
I'm really sorry.
I will help you to get
insurance compensation.
Looks like you are afraid of cold.
Yesterday I went out for a drink
with my colleagues.
When I came out,
the windows were all smashed.
You look like that fellow that ran
away after smashing the windows.
But it seems that I have made
a mistake.
That...How much longer?
People in my profession tends to
make a few enemies.
Our job is quite similar to the
policemen's.
We target those people
who cause troubles, ...
... after drinking and  use violence
on their wives and children.
I'm asking you
when we are reaching.
You are already an adult
but why are you so impatient?
Anyway, why are you going to
Ja Ae School?
I will be teaching the children.
Really? Are you a teacher?
So you know sign language, right?
What's the meaning?
I think I know
why you have so many enemies.
Contact me after you have estimated
the compensation amount.
Don't try to do something different.
I am in extremely good terms
with the policemen of this city.
Hello.
This is the Headmaster Office.
Ask the Admin Head to
come over for a while.
So you are a student of Prof. Gim?
Yes. He's my professor in the
university.
Prof. Gim painted this portrait
for me.
I see.
I'm fully confident of the
calibre of Prof. Gim's students.
I was in the same class with
Prof. Gim till 3rd year of high school.
If he didn't choose to specialize
in fine arts,
most likely we would be studying
in the same university.
You don't have to be so polite.
I have to.
You are going to be our teacher soon.
Of course, I need to be polite to you.
Admin Head.
This is our new art teacher from
Seoul, recommended by Prof. Gim.
I'm Gang In Ho.
Looking forward to working with you.
Is this the first time you see
an identical twin?
I'm sorry.
It's all right.
I believe most people who see us
for the first time will have the
same reaction as you.
You must be very tired after
traveling such long distance.
Take a good rest this weekend
and start work next week.
The admin head will make your
arrangements for other matters.
Hyeong, how should we handle
that matter?
Admin Head, this is a school.
Headmaster,
how should we proceed with it?
Didn't I mention that
he's recommended by Prof. Gim?
Are you playing with me?
You are from Seoul,
but why are you so dumb?
Originally, you need to give a big note.
But since you are recommended by
Prof. Gim, 5 small notes will do.
- Are you asking money from me?
- Then, do you think this teacher's
position comes free?
You are really...
Remember, no cheque.
School Development Fund.
I heard everyone must contribute to it.
So, how much do they need?
50 million Won.
Not 5 million Won
but 50 million Won!
I heard it was already a discount since
I was recommended by my professor.
Oh my god!
Where could I get so much money?
Nice drawing.
You have an aptitude
for drawing.
The lesson has started for some time.
Why are you only here now?
I'm talking to you.
Are you saying Min Su?
That child's younger brother lost his life
in a train accident a few days ago.
That child definitely is not in the
right state of mind now.
His only brother died.
How can he not be depressed?
Not only Min Su. I feel that the rest
of the children are a bit strange too.
What is so strange about?
It's not easy to explain clearly
in a few words.
Mr. Gang, this is your first time
teaching in such a school, right?
You cannot treat the children here
like any normal children.
When one has a disability,
one will feel incomplete.
I have been in contact with these
children for more than 10 years.
But until now, they are still not
opening their minds to me.
Jeon Min Su.
His father is mentally retarded.
His mother's whereabouts is unknown.
Jin Yu Ri.
With an intellectual disability grade 3
and a mental age of 8 years old.
Have to watch her
as she has a huge appetite.
Gim Yeon Do.
She's is an orphan...
I just knock off from work.
Have you taken your dinner?
I have eaten a little.
Song In? Have you feed her?
I just feed her a few spoons.
Why did you feed her so little?
She said she doesn't like to eat
rice & has been asking for pizza.
If she wants to eat, just buy it
for her. How much can that cost?
Don't worry.
I won't starve your daughter.
When you reach home, remember
to check your bank account.
You got the money?
When you withdraw the money, you
must get the new coins from them.
Anyone inside?
By any chance,
did something happen?
What are you doing here?
Just now, there were some strange
sounds coming from inside.
But that doesn't mean you can go
inside a ladies' toilet.
What if a child passes by and
saw it?
Looks like you are new and don't
know the situation here well.
The children often made strange
sounds when they are bored.
Furthermore, because they are
deaf, they yell even louder.
I'm going to lock up the main gate.
You better get going.
Recently, the investigation has
given me headaches.
That bunch of kids always cause
troubles for me as well.
Our kids have been a pain
in the neck to Officer Jang, right?
Can't really say
it's a pain in the neck.
Teaching good morals to children
is also part of policeman's duty.
The key is that
the kids should listen.
I told them many times not to leave
their rooms at night.
No use saying to them.
They can't hear it.
You are right.
It's all right. Come in.
Development fund
is not against any law.
Isn't it, Officer Jang?
Of course. If I earn enough,
I will also contribute to
the school development fund.
I heard you are from Seoul.
Are you adapting well?
This Mu Jin City, except for
the year in year out fog,
there isn't really many things here.
It's okay. I'm good.
That, how about a drink with me
when you have the time?
Although this city looks pretty
dilapidated,
there are still enjoyment places
for men.
The little fishes here are not bad.
Min Su, it's impolite to look at
teacher using that eye expression.
Stand up!
Stand straight. Didn't I teach you
before that
you should still show courtesy
when you are being beaten?
Get up, Min Su.
Hello.
Mr. Pak, what happened?
Please wait a moment.
This kid secretly left the dormitory
at night.
And even brought along
two other girls with him.
I was so worried
that I didn't sleep at all last night.
This kid's younger brother also
died because of this reason.
Mr. Pak,
the Headmaster is looking for you.
Min Su, can't you understand
my feelings?
Open your mind to me and enjoy
each other company.
Isn't it better that way?
What are you doing?
Quick, get in.
Get in! Hey, you!
Come down quickly.
What do you plan to do?
What if you fell out of the window?
What's the matter?
Sorry. I have frightened you.
I did this because I was worried.
What are you doing?
I am educating the children.
Hey auntie, who are you? Who allows
you to educate them in this way?
I am the dormitory superintendent,
Yun Ja Ae.
I am in charge of
after-school education.
This is not something
you should interfere with.
You are dunking the child's head
into the washing machine and
you asked me to ignore it?
Are you crazy?
I heard there's a new teacher
from Seoul.
So it's a fellow who cannot
differentiate between urine & shit.
Are you looking down on me because
you think I come from backwater?
In Seoul, I have a number of friends
who are prosecutors and lawyers.
If you dare to do it again,
I will make sure
you are thrown into jail.
Heed my advice.
Yeon Do.
Hello.
Which ajussi?
Oh, that ajussi.
What's the matter? I thought the
repairing fees had long been settled.
Are you saying
beating up disabled children?
This is not a discrimination,
it's completely an atrocity.
The child is in such a bad state.
Ajussi, what have you being doing?
Please call her parents first.
This child is an orphan.
I have heard it from the Admin Head.
Miss Yun Ja Ae's teaching
method is bad.
Mr. Gang, it is understandable
for you to be angry when
your students are met with
such encounters.
I had already issued
a harsh warning to Miss Yun Ja Ae.
So could you be magnanimous
and forgive her this time?
Miss Yun Ja Ae
had already reflected on it.
She also want to personally apologize
to student Yeon Do.
But it seems that Yeon Do didn't go
back to her bedroom last night.
Nothing happens to the child, right?
We are worried over her.
Actually, her condition is quite bad.
So I admitted her into hospital.
Is that so?
Is it very serious?
No, it's not. They said she can
be discharged tomorrow.
You don't have to be too worried.
We will handle the discharge
procedure.
But which hospital is she in?
As Yeon Do is not feeling well,
she is unable to come today.
How about...
You draw me and I draw you.
Why? You are unwilling?
I have bruises and wounds.
Don't worry.
I will draw you beautifully.
Ajussi, where are you now?
Can you come over right now?
I am getting off from work now.
I will rush over to the hospital.
It may be inconvenient to
discuss it in hospital.
Let's meet outside.
- Okay, I know.
- Okay.
What's the matter?
Yeon Do,
she... was almost violated.
Furthermore, the Headmaster
was the perpetrator.
He forced himself on her but
I think he wasn't successful.
Because the child was too young.
It's too ridiculous!
Who said that?
Did you have a drink too many?
How many glasses did you drink?
Yeon Do wrote this for me
last night.
- Was it really the Headmaster?
- Yes.
Yeon Do wasn't the only one who
was violated.
There were a few perpetrators.
A teacher by the name Pak Bo Hyeon
had even sexually abused boys.
Can't you understand my feelings?
- Was the Headmaster the only
person who did those acts?
- Headmaster, & also Admin Head
as well as Mr. Pak Bo Hyeon.
Then,
we have to made a police report.
The Police was the one who sent
the children who reported the case
back to the school.
They took revenge on those
children by violently beating them up.
That dormitory superintendent,
Yun Ja Ae, who beat up Yeon Do,
is found to be the adopted daughter
of the founder of Ja Ae School.
In other words, she is
the Headmaster's younger sister.
Is there a girl named Gim Yeon Do
in the patient list?
And even more ridiculous is
that Yun Ja Ae and
the Headmaster are lovers.
When she snipped off
Yeon Do's hair, she told her this.
If she dared to seduce the
Headmaster, she will be killed.
Ajussi.
Wait a moment.
MU JIN Human Rights Center.
We understand that you were
violated by the Headmaster of
Ja Ae School last Thursday.
Could you give an account of
what happened?
That day, after school,
I went to my bedroom to change
my clothes.
Then, I went to play on the field.
My playmate Yu Ri said that
she needs to go to toilet.
As she was not back
after a long time,
I decided to go back to school
to look for her.
Then, I saw the Headmaster & he
seems to asking me to come over.
He brought me
to the Headmaster Office.
The TV was on.
I saw pictures of
naked man and woman.
After the Headmaster came in,
he removed my pants.
Anyone inside?
Anyone calling?
It's drizzling outside
the windows now.
The sound of raindrops
that fall on the leaves,
is like whispering to us that
the cold winter has ended.
My listener friends, why not open
the windows and listen to the
sound of raindrops?
The first song I'm playing is one
suitable to be heard on a raining day.
Let's listen to "A Thornbush"
by Jo Sung Mo.
Everything is fine now.
Yeon Do said she had seen it too.
If you dare to tell this to others,
I will kill you.
Looks like you are new & don't
know the situation here well.
The children often made strange
sounds when they are bored.
- Father!
- You're here, mom.
Why did you take so long to open
the door? What are you doing?
Don't tell me because you are
teaching the deaf children,
so you become deaf as well.
Why didn't you tell me
before coming over?
I'm coming to my son's house, do I
still need to make an appointment?
This place is not a hotel.
But how can you bring a sick child
over here?
You...Have you forgotten?
Today is Song In's mother's
death memorial day.
How's the school?
Just like that.
What's wrong?
Are you being disregarded?
You just have to tolerate a bit.
In the first place, country folks
are a bit xenophobic.
What's that?
I heard that your school's headmaster
loves cymbidium.
Prof. Gim has mentioned before that
your school's headmaster is a
person with wide connections.
I heard that a few teachers that
were before you
were transferred to Seoul after getting
into the headmaster's good books.
Mom, do you know
what those people really are?
- Mom, let me tell you. Those people...
- Do you think I would think
people who sell teaching positions
are good people?
Do you know
where I got those money?
Those money came from the
deposit money for the house.
Did you return the house? Is that
how the remittance came about?
Then what was your initial thinking?
I can't possibly go and steal
money, right?
You never remit any money to us.
How on the earth can I get that
large sum of money?
I understand
but why did you return the house?
You really...You are still acting like
you are the head of this family.
During the times you were wondering
aimlessly for the sake of drawing.
Have you forgotten
it was Song In's mother and I...
...who raised Song In & provided
for your living expenses?
Before Song In's mother died, she was
still worrying over Song In and you!
Father, are you quarreling with
grandmother?
Don't say anymore.
You just focus on
teaching the students,
don't be a busybody, and do a
good job in your own area of work.
Song In, are you all right?
Mom. Quickly.
Here's the medicine.
- Song In.
- Come, breathe in.
- One more time. Good.
- Good.
I have found a house near to
where we lived previously.
Although it's a bit small,
it's good enough for
Song In and I to live in.
In Ho, don't bother about other things.
Just think of Song In, please?
We are putting up a formal application
to dismiss Chairman of Ja Ae School,
and to punish the people who sexually
abused the children.
I'm very sorry.
May I interrupt for a while?
Those sexual abuses... were they
done during lesson times?
In other words, was it something
that happened during class?
Looking at this video clip,
it's clear that
- the children were abused after school.
- So, it was after school.
If it's after school,
then it's not under our administration.
What?
Since Mr. Gim committed those acts
after school,
why should it be
under our administration?
Such things should come
under City Hall.
The Headmaster, the Admin Head
and also a teacher
sexually abused students
in the school.
Don't tell me this is not under
the Education Department?
Let me put in another way.
Ja Ae School is indeed come under
our control. But Ja Ae Hostel...
is a school dormitory and
should come...
...under the City Hall Social
Welfare Department.
After school, the children are
managed by the school dormitory.
Therefore, you should go to the
City Hall.
I already went to the City Hall.
People over at the City Hall said
since the sexual abuses happened
in the school compound, we should
seek advice from Education Dept...
I have told you, after school incidents
are not under our administration.
Ajumma. (ajumma -
addressing a middle aged woman)
The children encountered such
things in the school & all of you...
kept saying that it's not under you.
Tell me exactly who is in charge?
Don't tell me it's under the Blue House?
Or how about the White House?
Of course is City Hall.
Why aren't you investigating?
The children was sexually abused
in school. Furthermore, these acts
were done by the Headmaster.
Shouldn't that be investigated?
Of course we should investigate.
Then why aren't you investigating?
Miss Seo, that Headmaster is
an elder of Mu Jin Church.
He's a devoted Christian and also
a reputable person in this region.
That's why I brought you the DVDs &
written records of children's statements.
Here are all these evidences.
Why are you not taking any action?
How can we just based on what
were said by the
deaf children & arrest that person?
Moreover, that person just received
a certification of commendation from
the Governor a few days ago.
Furthermore, as there are problems
concerning human rights recently,
we also cannot simply anyhow
arrest people.
Miss Seo, you should know better
than me regarding the last point.
They had done such things to the children.
Why are you bullshitting on human rights?
If all of you going to continue
like this,
I will take the issue straight to the
Prosecutor Office.
If you really do that,
I'm really grateful to you.
Don't jump into conclusions thinking
we don't want to investigate.
Without orders from the Prosecutor,
we also cannot take any actions.
I'm unhappy. I think I should consider
grooming my son to be a prosecutor.
Hello.
Miss Seo, I'm Yeong Hun.
Seoul Television Station has
contacted us & they are interested
to do a coverage on this case.
- Really?  -Yes. They are on their
way here. You come back quickly.
I understand.
I'll be there right away.
Come here. Come here.
Brat.
Min Su, get up. Why are lying there?
Quickly get up.
Where are Yeon Do and Yu Ri?
Aren't you friends with them?
Don't mumble. Speak up.
Quickly speak up.
This is so frustrating. I'm asking you
to speak up! You Dumb Nut!
You are always mumbling.
How will I understand them?
This kid is really...
Mr. Pak, you are getting old.
Looks like the children are no
longer afraid of you.
Mr. Pak.
This is the Headmaster Office.
Find a quieter place.
They will really receive punishment?
Yes, I promise you.
Why did your younger brother go
to railway track early in the morning?
Can you tell us what happened to
your younger brother before he died?
When Mr. Pak Bo Hyeon was off from
work, he asked us to follow him home.
Although I don't wish to, I can't reject
because he will beat me up.
Why? You want to go first?
You're too noisy.
I already said not to make noise.
I cannot concentrate.
Didn't I say to you before that
making noise is not a courtesy act?
I did not allow you to make noise.
I asked you to wait quietly for
your turn. You didn't hear that?
Come over! You this brat!
I'm not sure how long it was.
Min Su!
He took off my undergarment.
And then came on top of me...
Can't you resist or escape?
If I resist,
I will be beaten the whole night.
Did that sort of thing happened before?
In the teacher's house and also
the dormitory's bathroom.
My younger brother was weak.
After undergoing that sort of thing,
he was under great pain and
cannot really walk.
Officer Jang, what are you doing?
You have the right to engage a lawyer
and...
...also the right to remain silent
with evidences against you.
Did you arrest me because of
what you saw on TV?
They fabricated it. That wasn't me.
Do you believe I'm that type of person?
I'm an elder with Mu Jin Church and
a devoted Christian.
Officer Jang, you also knew this thing.
Let me go.
Do you know who you are arresting?
I'm a friend of your superintendent.
What's your name?
- I'm not done with you.
- Hyeong, you don't have to worry.
Nothing will happen to you.
God will bless you.
Don't worry.
I definitely will not let off...
...the people who tarnish
my brother's reputation.
- What bad luck today.
- Officer Jang.
Hyeong.
Let go of me.
Officer Jang,
you really don't believe in me?
How could you treat us like this?
We have given you so many gifts.
This has caused a big commotion at
the Mu Jin Prosecutor Office today.
If we don't handle this properly,
not only I will be finished, but also
my superiors.
I'm not going to repeat.
Please stop grumbling.
Listen carefully to what I have
to say.
Make use of all your connections.
Search for a lawyer who started
his career as a judge.
He must be at least a judge of
ministerial grade.
It's even better if his birth place
is Mu Jin.
Don't keep doing useless things
such as screaming aloud
that you are maligned. You can
do that during your prayers.
Before such a lawyer is found, you
should act ignorant & be well-behaved
just like those children who were
sexually abused by you. Understand?
Dear residents of Mu Jin, Elder Lee
Gang Bok & Elder Lee Gang Seok
have over the last 10 over years,
worked hard day and night, and
contributed selflessly to our
Mu Jin Church and Mu Jin City.
They believe & serve Jesus, & care
for those pitiful disabled children.
They devoted their whole life
to charity.
Yet these dishonest people
maligned our elders.
We absolutely cannot
forgive them.
It's a blessing in disguise.
I'm begging all residents.
The children cannot hear all these.
Both Elders spent all their time &
effort on our church & Mu Jin City.
Yeong Hun sunbae. Have you...
...checked out the background of
their lawyer?
That lawyer is called Hwang U Sik. He's
a famous & talented lawyer in Mu Jin.
He graduated from
Mu Jin High School
and was the best law graduate
from Seoul University.
He was once a ministerial grade judge.
He opened a law firm just recently.
It seems that this is his first law case.
- "Jeon Gwan Ye U".
What is "Jeon Gwan Ye U"? (Jeon
Gwan Ye U ~ privileges of former post)
There's an informal arrangement for
a retired judge with this ministerial grade
to receive special treatment for
their first case in private practice.
Why are these two people so identical,
both in appearance and character?
I lived in disgrace
over the last few days.
I reflected on why God is making me
go through this type of suffering.
My father, Mr. Lee Jun Beon.
Because he pitied
those deaf and mute,
he used all his savings to build
this Ja Ae School.
It's already more than 50 years. Since
childhood, my brother & I have never
forgotten a saying from our father.
"Treat these pitiful lambs well."
We cannot hear.
Please find us an interpreter.
Silence.
Your Honor.
They cannot hear you
asking them to be silent.
In court,
if you speak without permission,
you will be ordered to leave
the courtroom.
I am Seo Yak Jin who works at
Mu Jin Human Rights Center.
This is a court case involving
the hearing-impaired.
To assist these disabled people,
please arrange for
a sign language interpreter.
Seo Yak Jin, please retire
from the courtroom.
Objection.
Police guards,
what are you doing there?
Quickly, take her away.
Objection. I object to it.
Your Honor, objection.
Did I say the wrong thing?
Starting from now,
even if it's a whisper,
I will also follow the law strictly
and take action on you.
Defendant, please continue.
Jesus will protect you.
Amen.
What? Rape.
You, this despicable person. In your eyes,
you can only see those dirty things?
Ajumma, what are you doing?
Where did this wretch girl pop up from?
Who are you exactly?
I'm Lee Gang Seok's wife.
What are you trying to do?
- You this wretch!
- Don't be like this.
How dare you sue my husband?
You thought that
we can be easily bullied?
- Ajumma. - I won't let you have
your way, you wretch!
- Let go of me.
- You this devil.
Let go of me!
If your husband has done those
things, even if you kneel & beg
for forgiveness for a long time,
he will still not be forgiven.
She still dare to behave
so crazily towards me.
Ajussi, you are really different.
She spitted on your face & you just
calmly asked her why she did that.
Can I stay in your office
this period of time?
Why?
Don't tell me you ran away from home.
Fired?
These people think that they could
just dismiss people as they wish.
Ajussi, you don't have to worry.
I will make sure they are punished by
the law & you can get back your job.
I really envy you.
You live such a simple life.
They really look down upon people.
My life is also not as smooth sailing
as you thought.
I was only concerned with the latest
fashion & never go for a proper date.
Always getting zeros in school.
Cannot find any job.
And with this meagre salary from
my current job...
Ajussi. Have you regretted...
participating in such a thing?
Mom, you are really amazing. You
know that I receive my salary today.
I have remitted to you in the morning.
Visit the bank to check it out.
Yes, everything is well.
No. You come over. I'm very busy.
A lot of work in school.
After this busy period,
I will find time to come home.
I swear by Almighty God that the
evidence I shall give will be the truth,
the whole truth and nothing
but the truth.
If I withhold any truths,
I will be punished by the law.
Witness O Jae Sik.
Defendant lawyer,
you can start examination.
Mr. O Jae Sik.  What is your area
of work in Ja Ae School?
I'm the security guard and
also do night-duty.
How long have you been working
in this area?
About 5 years.
So in the last 5 years,
you are by the side of the
Headmaster and Admin Head.
What is your opinion of them?
They are both good people.
- And they also take good care of me.
- Your Honor, objection.
These questions are unrelated
to the case.
Objection sustained.
Please only raise questions
related to this case.
Do you patrol around the school
every night?
Yes. I patrol every 3 hours at night.
Right. So over the last 5 years,
did you see any instances where
the Headmaster & the Admin Head
called the children individually
into the Headmaster Office & Admin
Head Office respectively after school?
I didn't see any such instances.
Sign language interpreter,
please let them know clearly
that if they continue to noisy, I will
ask them to leave the courtroom.
You mentioned before that on the day
when Gim Yeon Do was nearly violated,
you met Gang In Ho
in front of the toilet, right?
Yes.
What did he say to you?
He said he heard a child's voice
coming from inside the toilet.
So what did you do?
He asked me to check it out.
So I pushed open the toilet's door,
and stepped in to check.
Was there anyone inside?
No one.
Okay. I'm done with my questioning.
Prosecutor,
it's your turn to cross examine.
Witness, where did you work before
this current job?
I previously worked as a security guard
at Mu Jin Primary School.
Why did you decide to transfer to
this special school?
From what I know, you earn
a lower salary at this special school
compared to the previous one.
That was because...
Because when you're in
Mu Jin Primary School,
you were caught stealing
school's properties.
It is still on police records.
Is it true?
You were dismissed by the school
and was unemployed for 3 years.
Your Honor. The Prosecutor is asking
questions not related to this case.
No, it's related. Because there exists
some kind of promise
between the school and its staff.
That's why such immoral thing
is connived.
People are kept completely in the dark
and it was not uncovered till now.
It's even possible that this is the key
to solving this whole case.
Objection overruled.
Please continue.
How did you get the job
in this school?
It definitely not easy getting in
relying on your curriculum vitae.
I was introduced by an associate.
That's right. Because you were
introduced by an associate.
Also you gave money in the name
of the school development fund.
Finally you got this post & started
work in the school.
But what if this case causes the
school to close down.
You will lose everything and
become homeless.
Was that the truth?
I'm done with my questions.
Witness, are you the doctor that came
with the staff of Human Rights Center?
Yes.
What's the outcome of the
examination?
There are symptoms of
inflammation in her genitalia.
Her hymen was already torn.
Is sexual abuse the only way in
which a young girl's hymen is torn?
No. Cycling or masturbation
may tore it too.
As a gynecologist,
- you must have examined
many patients who are sexually
abused.  - Yes.
Normally, what's the condition of
such patients?
The genitalia tear will be more
serious.
Furthermore, they will feel humiliated
and almost out of their mind.
So when you were examining Jin Yu Ri,
what was her condition?
She was munching biscuits.
She was extremely calm even
to an extent
that I thought she wasn't violated.
She also didn't have
any bruises or wounds.
In other words, you don't think
she had been violated, right?
Yes.
I'm done with my questions.
This doctor is the general secretary
of Mu Jin Girls' High School Alumni.
That woman is the Chairman.
Your Honor.
What is this?
This is the preliminary analysis report
for Jin Yu Ri written by the witness.
Am I holding the actual
preliminary analysis report?
In other words, you had written
2 analysis reports, right?
That was because...
You just have to answer Yes or No.
Then let us take a look at the
first analysis report.
The patient's genital injury and
the tearing of her hymen
were not caused by recent
sexual intercourse.
But in subsequent analysis report,
you said that sexual intercourse
was highly unlikely the cause.
Instead, you wrote that it was
caused by other reasons.
This is different from the first report.
What's the reason for judging that it wasn't
due to sexual intercourse in the 2nd report?
- What's the reason for changing the
analysis report?  - At that time, I...
didn't know that it will have implications
on such a serious matter.
Don't tell me that
a doctor's analysis report
will differ according to
how serious the matter is.
In the first analysis report,
you wrote that it wasn't due to
recent sexual intercourse.
Then, it means that you believe she had
sexual intercourse in the past. Am I right?
Witness,
why did you change your testimony?
Is it really because of the seriousness
of this case?
No, it is not.
I felt that the damage to her hymen
was not something that happened
recently.
Instead, it had happened at least
5 years ago.
If it's 5 years ago, the victim was
only 9 years old.
It's really too young for her to have
intercourse. Therefore...
I like to ask
Is it really possibly for her to be involved
in intercourse with an adult man?
Even if it's possible,
without the consent & coordination
by the female, this sort of thing
couldn't happen, isn't it?
Silence.
Min Su, you have no appetite? Do you
want me to order other food for you?
Yeon Do, you are not hungry?
When I was young, I came to the
beach before with my father & mother.
That was before I was deaf...
At that time, I heard the sound of
wave crashing into the shore.
But now it's very quiet.
The best & most beautiful things
in the world cannot be seen or
even touched.
They must be felt with the heart.
This is a quote by Helen Keller,
and it's my favorite quote.
What did she say?
She said it would be good
if I were her father.
if you were her mother.
Hey, she's already talking
like an adult.
Until now, I don't even had
a proper love relationship.
How can she match us together?
Ajussi, don't dream.
There's not a hope for you.
Why?
Why don't you answer me?
Quickly answer me.
I am the one who has been taken
advantage of, not you.
Who said you had been taken
advantage of?
You said it yourself.
First, the examination of the
defendants.
Looking at the child who is sitting
here. What's your feelings?
With things being in this state.
In any case, she was victimized
by you all.
I am always curious who was the
one who spread these absurd rumors?
But it looks like I could vaguely
remember the child's face...
- Defendant.
You mean you cannot remember clearly
that child that sued you for sexually abuse?
Although I saw her a few times...
The Headmaster is not wrong.
That child is also intellectually disabled.
So I also remembered caressing
her head a few times.
Defendant Pak Bo Hyeon,
how about you?
She belongs to my class.
I have no reason not to know her.
I have always love and treasure
these children.
Among them,
Who was the one who removed
your clothes and made you painful?
All 3 of them.
How many times?
Many times. Many, many times.
Do you still remember
when it first started?
It started when I was in Primary 3.
Admin Head would always give me
money every time he did that thing to me.
Every time he would give me
1000 Won to buy biscuits.
Admin Head removed my pants.
It's too painful.
I said no and pushed him away.
Because I was too scared,
I tried to escape.
However, Admin Head grabbed hold
of me and pinned me on the table.
He also tied up my hands and legs.
They were all lies.
Your Honor, she's a lunatic!
Don't believe in her words.
They were all lies.
- How dare you say such lies!
- Silence.
Did someone incite you to
say all these?
- Exactly who incited you to say
such lies?  - Silence!
Settlement?
The children were sexually abused.
Why should there be a settlement?
Yes, according to the Prosecutor.
Children who are 13 years old & above
and suffered from sexually abuse.
If they agree to a settlement,
their testimony will all become invalid.
If one really met with such a thing,
will one agrees to settle outside court?
Yeon Do's parents are gone.
Nothing much can be done.
But Min Su and Yu Ri's parents
are mentally retarded.
They are really a pack of beasts.
Bullying those children with no parents.
Once Yu Ri and Min Su agree to
the settlement,
then what's left will only be
the Headmaster's sexually abuse
case on Yeon Do.
Professor.
I'm really very sorry to ask
to see you so abruptly.
No, it's okay.
I should have visited you.
I roughly heard about the case
from Lawyer Hwang.
I was the one who recommended
you to that school.
So I am sandwiched in the middle
and my position is a bit awkward.
I am sorry.
You don't have to feel apologetic
to me.
But if this case continues to drag,
you also won't get any benefits
out of it.
This is the money that you donated
to the school previously.
And we added a bit more to it.
I hope to settle the case with
Yeon Do.
Appreciate if Mr. Gang could help out.
If you are willing to help us,
we will be responsible for the expenses
to send Yeon Do to university.
We will also send her abroad
to further study.
Of course,
you should continue to draw.
I feel it's a pity if you have to give up
your future in this area.
I have already made arrangements
for you to join a school in Seoul.
You just have to work hard for
another 1 to 2 terms over there.
I have already settled it
with the school.
They would convert you to
permanent staff.
I'm sorry, Professor.
I have some other things on.
I'm leaving first.
Mr. Gang.
You should give a thought to
your daughter who's still young.
I heard your daughter is quite sick.
The negotiation for settlement
had been completed.
It seems that Yu Ri's father
was convinced by his relatives.
You know it very well.
Yu Ri's father is mentally retarded.
So...
Yeon Do, are you confident to
articulate your statement clearly?
What are you doing here?
You said that you were very busy at
school & so you couldn't return home.
Is this place your school?
Are you thinking that people
might not believe in your words,
that's why you chose not to tell me?
Think of yourself first.
Take good care of your family.
It's no use saying the right things.
I have to go in.
To you, is this child more important
than your daughter Song In?
I was present when the child met
with that sort of thing.
But I was helpless.
If I were to give up now, I'm not confident
to be a good father to Song In.
Gim Yeon Do.
You said that the Headmaster
violated you.
Was that the truth?
Yes.
Are you usually in good terms
with the Headmaster?
No.
Then how would you know that
the person who violated you
was the Headmaster?
Because I met him a few times
in school.
Furthermore, that person dragged me
into the Headmaster Office that night.
In that case, between the 2 persons
over there,
which one is the Headmaster?
Objection.
He cannot request the victim
to confirm the identity of a suspect
whom had already been confirmed.
This is a very important question.
She said that she was violated
by the Headmaster.
To the victim, it's just an encounter.
However, if we look from the
perspective of
the Headmaster and
his younger twin brother.
It's possible that the real culprit
wasn't the Headmaster but
his younger brother.
Then Headmaster Lee Gang Seok
would no longer be a suspect.
Objection overruled.
Please continue.
Between the two,
who's the one who harm you?
Your Honor, Yeon Do requests to
take a closer look at them.
Agree.
Prisoner with serial number 4022
is indeed the defendant,
Headmaster Lee Gang Seok.
But, How did you recognize him?
Does Lee Gang Seok have
any special features?
Headmaster and Admin Head
both do not know sign language.
But on the night when Headmaster
did that to me in the toilet,
and every time when he did bad things
on Yu Ri,
he would always made one hand sign.
What's the hand sign?
If you dare to tell others,
I will kill you.
I performed this hand sign
to both of them.
Only one of them understood this
and his facial expression changed.
Hence, this person must be the
Headmaster.
Yeon Do,
according to your testimony,
after dinner, on your way home
after buying a bowl of noodles,
you noticed that Yu Ri had
disappeared, right?
After that,
you saw the Headmaster
sexually abusing Yu Ri in the
Headmaster Office.
Was that the truth?
Yes.
In this hearing,
on your way to the dormitory,
you heard faint music coming
from the Headmaster Office.
So you changed your direction and
walked towards it to find out more, right?
Yes.
Your Honor.
This is it.
Faint music.
Everyone knows that
Yeon Do is deaf.
But yet she could hear music.
This deaf child, upon hearing music,
walked towards it.
When she reached
the source of the music,
she saw the Headmaster raping
her friend.
Your Honor.
This testimony is so absurd!
To come up with such absurd
testimony... She said she didn't lie.
She really heard very faint music.
It's a song from Jo Sung Mo.
Witness,
you have impaired hearing,
but you can still hear music, right?
Yes.
Yeon Do.
From now onwards, we are running
a test to check
whether you can hear music.
If you hear music,
please raise your hand.
Begin.
I recognized the witness's account.
Forensic Branch,
please submit a report to the court
as regards to Yeon Do's suspect
identification.
The next hearing is this Friday.
Prosecutor and Defendant Lawyer,
if you have new witnesses,
please reapply to court.
What did all those adults do to
these little children?
When you are done with it,
return home quickly.
Miss Seo.
Why are you here?
Looks like you have guessed
correctly.
Correct. That is the... contract.
When Min Su's grandmother
saw the money,
she immediately signed
the contract.
Really funny.
No matter how poor or
how illiterate you are,
it's your own grandchildren who met
with such a thing.
Just because of money, they agreed
to settle outside court.
Well, of course.
It's not something that
I cannot comprehend.
She has a son but he lies on the
hospital bed all day long.
Her daughter-in-law eloped.
Moreover, her grandchildren
are deaf and mute.
Even I feel that
God is a bit too much.
Teacher, when I'm giving my testimony,
can I have this in front of me?
I also want to give a good
performance just like Yeon Do.
But I'm not confident of myself.
So I have written them down here.
When Mr. Pak Bo Hyeon did that sort
of thing to my younger brother & me.
Min Su!
Originally,
you need to give a testimony.
But you cannot do it anymore.
Why?
Your grandmother has forgiven
Mr. Pak Bo Hyeon.
Those people begged your
grandmother to forgive them.
Your grandmother is a kind person,
so...
He killed my younger brother!
He killed him!
When he saw my brother and me,
he would beat us & remove our pants.
Min Su!
Who said to forgive him?
I have not forgiven him!
He didn't apologize to
my brother and me.
How could he be forgiven?
You promised that you would make
sure those people are punished.
Teacher,
didn't you make that promise?
I am sorry, Min Su.
I am sorry.
Yeon Do.
Why?
I have something to tell you.
What is it?
That time, I forgot to say that
when I was dragged into the
Headmaster Office, the picture that
was showing on the television...
That movie with nude man & woman.
Although I'm not certain, that man...
Will there really be that type of thing?
Even if there is,
it will not be left here.
Whe the Headmaster was arrested
so suddenly that day.
He didn't have the time to destroy it.
He could ask someone else to do it.
Who could he find? His wife?
His wife trusts him so much. Could he
let her know that he's a pervert?
Could he get his lover Yun Ja Ae
to do it?
That's right.
If Yun Ja Ae knew about it,
she would throw him into
the washing machine.
It's so nauseating.
The date on the video cassette tape
is consistent with the one in
Yeon Do's testimony.
You mentioned previously that
for child above 13 years old,
the case is closed after settlement
with the family.
The date was 14 March.
It means that Yu Ri hasn't reached
the age of 13 yet. In other words...
In other words,
if he sexually abused a child less
than 13 years old,
he could still be sentenced even
if there exists settlement.
Moreover,
with such clear-cut evidence,
Even if the defendant has
"Jeon Gwan Ye U",
it would also be useless.
The final trial is just a few days away.
Will there still be a retrial?
Even if there is a retrial,
we cannot show this evidence
in court.
Then what should we do?
Do not worry.
I will go and find the judge
personally,
and present this evidence.
The 3 defendants. Despite being
teachers of the deaf school,
they sexually abused the
young students.
It's an unpardonable criminal behavior.
And violated the social responsibility
of protecting disabled children.
Making these victims the targets
of their sexual pleasure,
sexually harassed them,
or violated them.
They should be punished severely.
But, the defendants have made
great contributions to the
development of the city,
and have no previous criminal records.
Furthermore,
the families of victim Jun Yu Ri
and victim Jeon Min Su
had already reached a settlement
with the defendants.
For the sake that the defendants had
taken care of their children before,
they had written a plea for the defendants.
With consideration of all the above,
the following sentences are meted out.
Defendant Pak Bo Hyeon.
Sentenced to 8 months of imprisonment
and 2 years on probation.
Defendant Lee Gang Bok.
Sentenced to 6 months of imprisonment
and 1 year on probation.
Defendant Lee Gang Seok.
Sentenced to 6 months of imprisonment
and 1 year on probation.
Prosector.
After the end of this trial,
carry out the procedures on the
release of the defendants.
You have really worked hard.
It's not really hard work.
I'm only doing justice to you.
Doing justice.
Justice always triumph.
This is so well said.
I am sorry.
I didn't fulfill my promise.
Take a look at the children
before going.
That judge.
I should go and express
my gratitude to him.
You don't have to go personally.
Jeon Gwan Ye U.
This is expected.
When I met him in classmate
gathering in the future,
I will treat him to drinks.
By the way,
how did you manage to bribe
the Prosecutor?
That person has no promotion
opportunities,
or any other options.
He's always roaming on the fringe.
In other words, he can no longer
carry on in this circle.
I told him that
I will give him a job in my law firm.
He was exuberant hearing it.
What's wrong? Are you hungry?
Min Su has gone to look for
Pak Bo Hyeon.
He said he wanted revenge.
I'm going over there now.
Please hurry over.
Ajussi, are you still on the phone?
Oh it's you, Min Su.
Are you thinking of me?
You are even drenched.
Let's go for a bath together.
Min Su! Min Su!
Min Su!
Anyone inside?
Min Su! Min Su!
Go to hell!
Min Su!
I treated you so well in the past.
How can you do this to me?
You this brat.
How dare you try to stab me!
I'm going to beat you to death!
Min Su!
You brat,
how can you do this to me?
We are from Mu Jin Police Station.
Listen up, everyone.
By gathering here,
you have violated Demonstration Act,
Article 6, Item 1 on illegal gathering.
All of you are illegally occupying
the roads.
And jeopardizing the lives of
the kind residents.
I hope you will disperse immediately.
Your demonstration now is
not allowed
and is an illegal demonstration.
Please disperse immediately.
I going to make the announcement again.
Now, everyone of you
is illegally occupying the roads.
If you don't disperse immediately,
we will charge you under the
Demonstration Act & Traffic Regulation.
That's right.
They cannot hear me.
What is going on?
Hurry to open fire.
Let go of me!
This child...
Neither can he hear nor can he speak.
This child is called Min Su.
He's a child who cannot hear
and cannot speak.
Everyone! This child's name
is called Min Su.
Neither can he hear
nor can he speak.
Everyone, please.
This child is called Min Su.
Neither can he hear nor can he speak.
Everyone,
this child is called Min Su.
This child...
One year later
Ajussi, how are you?
It seems like I haven't contacted you
for a long time.
Many things happened during
this period.
There are good ones
and bad ones.
Let me tell you the bad thing first.
We are still unsuccessful
with the appeal.
The main problem is still because of the
settlements that the families entered in.
The good thing is that many people
have come forward to help the children.
Because of them, the children who quitted
from Ja Ae School have a place to live in.
There are also people
who provided free food.
Yu Ri is undergoing
psychological treatment.
She is healthier now.
She is also more jovial these days.
And she will even teach me
sign language.
Yeon Do said that she wants to be
an art teacher when she grows up.
She said she wanted to me
like you helping sick children.
Once during dinner time,
I asked Yeon Do and Yu Ri,
what's the greatest difference
before
and after this incident?
The children said,
"We now know that
we are no difference from others."
"We are treasured by people too."
Watching these children
growing up gradually,
it comes to my mind that
the reason
why we are fighting so hard,
is not to change the world
but instead not to let the world
change us.
The weather has become colder.
Winter is cold
because it wants us to appreciate
the warmth from our surrounding
people. It's so precious!
Although we are not by your side,
I hope you can feel
the warmth given out by
the children and me.
I will pray for you.
Till 2011, a few of the perpetrators
have gone back to school.
The case had completed ended.
But to expose the truth,
they are still continue with the fight...